switzerland coming down the course
and this is andre look at that
hey yo
what's good
everyone welcome back to another vlog
like and subscribe and join the air squad
let's hit forty k before christmas
i think we got it
we are here back in corvatthe weather is beautiful
the park is perfectly shaped and it's going to be an awesome day
and so so we decided to come back here to curbach
yeah
because it's perfect weather
and it also has like
you can see here a lot of fresh snow
so i'm gonna do my tricks in the morning
do a little bit of training
jumps and rails
and in the afternoon we're gonna go and ski some powder
because i think there's a lot of powder here
and it's gonna be epic
i can't wait to ski powder after so
let's try and park now
i see in the morning park
and now the shadow is in the park
so it's not that good anymore
and i went for a quick lunch at the banana and the protein bar
and now we're back with the crew
um
skiing some pow
that's fabian
you've never seen him in the block
but he's the guy who's doing the air squad tv
on taylor club zoom
yeah
so i'm sure everyone
i'm shredding powder with him
because he's local
he's from silver plana
and he knows all the secret spots
so yeah
that's nice
also the snow is still perfect
i mean it's no two days ago
but it's still so soft and very fresh
and then also give the guy finn billis
you might know him from the world cups
you want to say something for the kiwis out there
and i'm like
yeah
so yeah
we're skiing some power
let's hit it
saturday
it's such a good day
yeah
i just
i was like what
let's go over there like
that come on it was a sender
yeah
there's a sunder
what's that actually
it's quite easy to send here
yeah
what do you think on the other side of the first one dude
that's so scary and free riding
when you have just no
i don't
yeah
i'm i'm filming so much
content with my gopro
but i don't care
i don't have to edit
sorry
freddie
nobody's going
so i'm gonna go first and get the nice tracks
see you
oh
that's a nice one
god
ah ha ha ha ha get it
that's the thing with powder skiing your legs
my legs are burning
last run of the day
look at this beautiful sunset
oh ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
if i was not
i was not sure if i should do the backflip
i was a bit scared
but then i started to take off
was perfectly right
yo
what are you doing here
aside
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
wow
we did a little quick stop here on the u pass with the nice sunrise
actually the sun is already down
uh
we were a little bit too late for the sun
it's already down
hey yo
where are you at
um
that was a fun day like training in the morning on the jump
yeah
the park is in good shape
and it was a lot of fun in the morning
doing some tricks
powder with my brother with fabian
he's doing the air squad tv
like cutting the squad tv and yeah
that was super fun
because i don't have the time during the year
like with all the competitions
i don't have a lot of time with like doing powder
so i really enjoy it
doing powder like today
when i have the time
and i think after my
uh
my career as a professional free skier in big and slope style
i might do some more
uh
powder like free and stuff
but that's ten years away now
it's time to enjoy it
slope style
big air and all the competitions
but now we should go back home
because i need to pack my stuff for china
back from corvage and i am currently packing my stuff for china
i'm leaving tomorrow for the second bigger world cup of the season
i also got a fresh package
i will open up the package before i leave to china
i want to see what's in here
i actually know you guys don't
so
that's nice
so my brother told me
this is the best powder ski ever
and then i wrote for me
i i need the ski
and now i have it so stoked to ski powder with this ski
hopefully during christmas
i got some time
and i think there's also a binding in it
oh ha ha
thank you so much vocal
have to ski that
but i really need to pack my stuff
i'm still not finished yet
and but i would say that was it for the vlog
make sure to subscribe
like the video
if you enjoyed it
i'll see you guys in china